{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Which one is a string?",
            "answers": [
                "5",
                "\"five\"",
                "false",
                "5.0"
            ],
            "correct": [1]
        },
        {
            "question": "What number base do computers use?",
            "answers": [
                "hexadecimal (base 16)",
                "decimal (base 10)",
                "octal (base 8)",
                "binary (base 2)"
            ],
            "correct": [3]
        },
        {
            "question": "a and not b\nWhat variables must be true for this condition to be true?",
            "answers": [
                "a = true, b = true",
                "a = true, b = false",
                "a = false, b = true",
                "a = false, b = false"
            ],
            "correct": [1]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one is a low-level programming language?",
            "answers": [
                "C#",
                "Python",
                "C",
                "Ruby"
            ],
            "correct": [2]
        },
        {
            "question": "int(input(\"How old are you?\")\nThis Python statement will raise an error. Why?",
            "answers": [
                "The statement is missing a bracket.",
                "The string must be surrounded in single quotes.",
                "The int() function cannot accept inputs.",
                "The statement is missing a semicolon (;) at the end."
            ],
            "correct": [0]
        },
        {
            "question": "[\"apple\", \"orange\", \"banana\", \"mango\", \"strawberry\"]\nWhich indices will return \"strawberry\"?",
            "answers": [
                "4",
                "5",
                "-1",
                "\"strawberry\""
            ],
            "correct": [0, 2]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does a Python file's name have to end with?",
            "answers": [
                ".python",
                ".p",
                ".pn",
                ".py"
            ],
            "correct": [3]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who created Python?",
            "answers": [
                "Tim Berners-Lee",
                "Bjarne Stroustrup",
                "Guido van Rossum",
                "Mark Zuckerberg",
                "Elon Musk"
            ],
            "correct": [2]
        },
        {
            "question": "What symbol must be used at the start of a Python comment?",
            "answers": [
                "//",
                "#",
                "comment",
                "->"
            ],
            "correct": [1]
        },
        {
            "question": "What symbols are used to define dictionaries in Python?",
            "answers": [
                "[]",
                "()",
                "{}",
                "dict()"
            ],
            "correct": [2, 3]
        }
    ]
}